const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "'He had a --- memory and he failed the memory test'. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.",
    answers: {
      a: "Week",
      b: "EKe",
      c: "Woke",
      d: "Weak",
    },
    //this answer should be d
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'The dress still looks --- even after two months of use.' - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.",
    answers: {
      a: "New",
      b: "Knew",
      c: "Gnu",
      d: "Know",
    },
    //this answer should be a
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'The money he gave me helped me to --- over the difficult period.' - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.",
    answers: {
      a: "Tied",
      b: "Tried",
      c: "Tide",
      d: "Tired",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'Eat everything on the plate, you should not --- food. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Waste",
      b: "Waist",
      c: "West",
      d: "Vest",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'He was asked to display his --- at the exhibition. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Wear",
      b: "Ware",
      c: "Where",
      d: "Were",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'You should --- the clothes well so they will dry faster. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Ping",
      b: "Cringe",
      c: "Ring",
      d: "Wring",
    },
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'This tree has a --- that is eight feet deep. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Root",
      b: "Route",
      c: "Rate",
      d: "Rite",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'He needs to take a --- as he has been exercising for two hours. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Broke",
      b: "Bray",
      c: "Brake",
      d: "Break",
    },
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'I have been wearing this --- of shoes for a long time. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Pear",
      b: "Pare",
      c: "Pair",
      d: "Payer",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c",
  },

  {
    question:
      "'The --- man delivered the letter today. - Fill in the blank with one of the four options.'",
    answers: {
      a: "Male",
      b: "Mail",
      c: "Melee",
      d: "May",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
];

export default questions;
